(Leonard:)So, listen, there was something
I was hoping to float past you.
(Leonard:)Now that Penny and I are engaged,
(Leonard:)I thought we might want to talk
about our living arrangements.
(Sheldon:)Of course.
(Sheldon:)She's spent many nights here,
and you're worried
(Sheldon:)about preserving the myth
of her virginity before the wedding.
(Leonard:)-I'm not.
-Good,
(Sheldon:)because not only
has that ship sailed,
(Sheldon:)if it hit an iceberg,
countless men would perish.
(Leonard:)Actually, this is about
where she and I are going to live.
(Sheldon:)What do you mean?
(Leonard:)Well, well, we might
want to live together.
(Sheldon:)Oh, yeah, well, I've already
given this some thought,
(Sheldon:)and I'm willing
to let Penny live with us
(Sheldon:)one day a week for a trial period.
(Sheldon:)Now, obviously,
not when she's made cranky
(Sheldon:)by the shedding
of her uterine lining.
(Leonard:)That's very sweet.